tubetrackr.com 2015-04-08

# Privacy Policy | tubetrackr.com

Your privacy is important to iLathys Pte Ltd. Tubetrackr is a brand of iLathys Pte Ltd. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that iLathys Pte Ltd collects, and the ways in which iLathys Pte Ltd uses that personal information.

#### Personal information collection

iLathys Pte Ltd may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website (including package purchased)
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including your email)
  * any other information that you send to iLathys Pte Ltd.

#### Using personal information

iLathys Pte Ltd may use your personal information to:

  * administer this website;
  * personalize the website for you;
  * enable your access to and use of the website services;
  * supply to you services that you purchase;
  * collect payments from you; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where iLathys Pte Ltd discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, iLathys Pte Ltd may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

#### Securing your data

iLathys Pte Ltd will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. iLathys Pte Ltd will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

#### Cross-border data transfers

Information that iLathys Pte Ltd collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which iLathys Pte Ltd operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

#### Updating this statement

iLathys Pte Ltd may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

#### Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. iLathys Pte Ltd is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

#### Contact iLathys Pte Ltd

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or iLathys Pte Ltd’s treatment of your personal information, please write:

  * by email to contact@ilathys.com or
  * by post to iLathys Pte Ltd, 71 Ayer Rajah Crescent #05-08, Singapore 139951
